Council on Foreign Relations Records: Studies Department Series, 1918-2004: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Subseries 3C: Staffing, 1925-2004; 32.32 linear feet 78 boxes
  - Maxwell, Kenneth, 1985-2004; 16 boxes (1 partial)
    - Study Program Files, 1988-1995; 11 boxes (1 partial)
      - Gunn, Gillian, Breakfast Update, Cuban Politics, 1991 December 11; 1 folder (Box 412, Folder 3)
      - Chile Conference, 1991-1992; more than 2 folders
        - General, 1992 January 17; 2 folders (Box 412, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Correspondence, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 412, Folder 6)
      - Lissakers, Karin, Breakfast Series, United States-Latin America Economic Relations, 1992 February 5; 1 folder (Box 412, Folder 7)
      - Knight, Alan, "The Historical Context of the Salinas Reforms," Mexico Round Table, 1992 February 10; 1 folder (Box 412, Folder 8)
      - Mindlin, José, Breakfast Series, Brazil's Economy, 1992 February 12; 1 folder (Box 412, Folder 9)
      - Mercosur Conference, 1992 March 16; 2 folders (Box 412, Folder 10 to 11)
      - Thorup, Cathryn, "Crossborder Coalitions in United States-Mexican Relations," Mexico Round Table, 1992 February 24; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 1)
      - Dominguez, Jorge, Breakfast Series, Cuba, 1992 February 26; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 2)
      - Utton, Albert, "Transboundary Environmental Issues," Mexico Round Table, 1992 March 9; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 3)
      - Ambassador Muñoz, Dinner Series, O.A.S., 1992 April 7; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 4)
      - Smith, Peter, Breakfast Series, Drug Policy, 1992 April 8; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 5)
      - Karl, Terry, Breakfast Series, Venezuela, 1992 April 9; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 6)
      - United States-Mexico, "Politics and Economic Integration: The New United States-Mexican Agenda," Breakfast Series, 1992 April 13; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 7)
      - de la Balze and Nogues, Dinner Series, Argentina, 1992 April 27; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 8)
      - Revkin, Andrew, Breakfast Series, Global Warming, 1992 May 6; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 9)
      - Peru, Workshop, 1992 May 11; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 10)
      - Fauriol, Georges, Breakfast Series, Haiti Politics, 1992 May 13; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 11)
      - Manning, Patrick, Breakfast Series, Trinidad and Tobago, 1992 May 15; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 12)
      - Feinberg, "New Agendas in the Hemisphere," Breakfast Series, 1992 June 10; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 13)
      - Breakfast Seminar on Brazil, 1992 October 26; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 14)
      - Brazil "Where Now?," Workshop, 1992 November 23; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 15)
      - Breakfast Seminar, "Argentina: Economic Reform", 1992 December 7; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 16)
      - Corporate Breakfast, "Economic Integration in North America", 1992 December 16; 1 folder (Box 413, Folder 17)
      - Asman, David, Robinson, Linda, and Russell, George, Breakfast Series, Items for a New Administration, 1993 March 17; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 1)
      - Brainard, Lawrence, Canovan, Chris, and Velasco, Andrés, Breakfast Series, "Economic Issues", 1993 March 31; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 2)
      - Sinkin, Richard, Mexico Round Table, "Changing Strategic Perspectives for Mexico in the Global Economy", 1993 April 1; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 3)
      - Castaneda, Jorge, Mexico Round Table, Political Situation and Presidential Succession, 1993 April 13; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 4)
      - Nierenberg, Claudia, Mendez, Juan, and Massing, Michael, Breakfast Series, "The Environment, Human Rights, and Drugs", 1993 April 14; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 5)
      - Teitelbaum, Michael, Sassen, Saskia, and Hoffman, Helga, Breakfast Series, Population, Migration, and Economic Development, 1993 May 5; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 6)
      - Hakim, Peter, Fauriol, Georges, and Dominguez, Jorge, Breakfast Series, "Policy Options: Cuba and Haiti", 1993 May 19; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 7)
      - Maxwell, Kenneth, Senior Fellow Breakfast Seminar Series, Clinton Latin American Policy, 1993 June 2; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 8)
      - Anderson, Kenneth, Tomlinson, Alan, and Vourvoulias-Bush, Alberto, Breakfast Series, "Policy Options: Central America", 1993 June 9; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 9)
      - Argentina's Economic Reforms Workshop, 1993 June 14; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 10)
      - Argentina's Economic Reforms Workshop, Background Papers, 1993 June 14; 1 folder (Box 414, Folder 11)
      - Cuba Study Group, 1993-1994; 5 folders
        - General Info, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 1)
        - Pérez, Jr., Louis A. and Valdés, Nelson, Cuba Study Group, Cuba's Future, 1993 October 28; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 2)
        - Pérez, Lisandro and Robbins, Carla Anne, Cuba Study Group, Cuba's Future, 1993 November 11; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 3)
        - Mesa-Lago, Carmelo, and Asman, David, Cuba Study Group, Cuba's Future, "The Cuban Economy after the Cold War", 1993 December 2; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 4)
        - Suchlicki, Jaime and Schulz, Donald, Cuba Study Group, Cuba's Future, "Policy Options", 1993 December 16; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 5)
      - Weintraub, Sidney, Mexico Round Table, NAFTA, 1993 December 8; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 6)
      - Rosas, Christina, Mexico Round Table, NAFTA, 1993 November 10; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 7)
      - Rapporteur Reports, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 415, Folder 8)
      - Redick, John R. and Scheinman, Lawrence, Nuclear Non-Proliferation Symposium, 1994 February 14; 1 folder (Box 416, Folder 1)
      - "Amazon TV Project", 1994 February 16; 1 folder (Box 416, Folder 2)
      - Oñate, Dr. Santiago, Corporate Series, "Issues in the Future of UNITED STATES-Mexican Relations", 1994 February 24; 1 folder (Box 416, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations Panel: "The Chiapas Rebellion and the Future of Mexico", 1994 February 25; 1 folder (Box 416, Folder 4)
      - Rodriguez, Julio Sosa, "Economic Reform and Growth in Venezuela", 1994 March 11; 2 folders (Box 416, Folder 5 to 6)
      - Thomas, Hugh, European Program Joint Seminar, "Britain and Europe", 1994 March 24; 1 folder (Box 416, Folder 7)
      - Senator Ledo, Breakfast Seminar, Opposition Victory in Mexico, 1994 April 4 and Valenzuela, Arturo, Breakfast Seminar, Chiapas and Problems of Democracy in Mexico, 1994 March 25, 1 folder (Box 416, Folder 8)
      - Research Mission to Cuba, 1994 April 6-11; 2 folders (Box 417, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Cuba Study Group, "Cuba's Future," Cuba Delegation, 1994 April 28; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 3)
      - Castenada, "Latin America After the Cold War", 1994 May 4; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 4)
      - Treviño, Jose Angel Gurria, Breakfast Seminar, The PRI and the Elections, 1994 May 5; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 5)
      - Menchu, Rigoberta, "Peace Process in Guatemala", 1994 May 6; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 6)
      - da Silva, Luiz Inácio Lula, Corporate Breakfast, Brazil Presidential Series, 1994 May 12, 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 7)
      - Aristide, Jean-Bertrand, Breakfast, Haiti, 1994 May 13; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 8)
      - "Jefferson and the Abbé," Public Lecture, 1994 May 17; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 9)
      - Haiti Policy Impact Panel, 1994 May-June; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 10)
      - Chamorro, Violeta, Breakfast Seminar, Nicaragua, 1994 September 27; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 11)
      - Robaina, Roberto, Cuba Update, Cuba's Future, 1994 October 5; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 12)
      - Constable, Pamela, United States Occupation, Haiti Working Group, 1994 October 6; 1 folder (Box 417, Folder 13)
      - Halperin, Mort, Cuba Update, Cuba's Future, 1994 October 11; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 1)
      - Schlesinger Arthur and Gardner, Richard, Iberian Seminar, 1994 October 24; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 2)
      - Brooke, James B., Breakfast Seminar, Brazil Election, 1994 October 27; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 3)
      - Hurbon, Laënnec and Trouillot, Michael Rolph, "Three Haitian Writers on Haiti," Haiti Working Group, 1994 November 9; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 4)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, "Brazil: Post-Election Analysis," Breakfast Series, 1994 November 16; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 5)
      - Gaspari, Elio and Teixeira, Roberto de Costa, Breakfast Seminar, Post-Election Analysis, 1994 November 17; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 6)
      - Altman, Roger, Corporate Breakfast, Clinton and Latin America, 1994 November 29; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 7)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, "Economic Future of the Americas," Breakfast Series, 1994 December 9; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 8)
      - Summit of the Americas, 1994 December 9-11; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 9)
      - NAFTA Study Group, 1994; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files, 1985-2004; 4 boxes (2 partial)
      - Americas Society, Council of the Americas, 1994-1999; 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 11)
      - Annual Report Materials, 1985-1993; portions of 2 boxes
        - 1985-1992, 1 folder (Box 418, Folder 12)
        - 1989-1993, 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 1)
      - BBC Brazil Program Proposal, 1993; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 2)
      - BBC TV Program, "The Essential History of Portugal", 1992 October; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 3)
      - Breakfast Series, 1989-1993; 2 folders
        - 1989-1990, 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous Information, 1993; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 5)
      - Cavallo, Domingo, Latin America Roundtable, 1993 February; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 6)
      - Collaborations with Corporate Program, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 7)
      - Conferences, 1993-1995; 2 folders
        - 1993, 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 8)
        - 1994-1995, 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 9)
      - Council of American Ambassadors Delegation to Cuba, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 10)
      - Culture and Foreign Policy Study Group, 1993; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 11)
      - Fuentes, Carlos, "The Buried Mirror", 1991; 1 folder (Box 419, Folder 12)
      - Isabel Documentary, 1992 September; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 1)
      - Latin American Program Activities, 1986-1991; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 2)
      - Latin American Program Advisory Committee, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 3)
      - Latin America Scholarship Program of American Universities (LASPAU), 1993-1997; 3 folders
        - 1993-1994, 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 4)
        - 1993-1997, 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 5)
        - 1994-1996, 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 6)
      - Madeira Conference, 1991 December; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 7)
      - Menem-New York Trip/Rapanelli, 1989; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 8)
      - Mexico Papers, 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 9)
      - Portuguese Museum, 1993; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 10)
      - Presentation on United States Army Support Role in the United States, 1991 February 11; 1 folder (Box 420, Folder 11)
      - Publications General Information, 1992-2001; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 1)
      - Travel Logistics, 1990; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 2)
      - Terverton-Lowenthal, "Global Change in Latin America", 1990; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 3)
      - United Nations Conference Presentation, "Portugal: Europe's Bridge to the Developing World?", 1991 December 9-11; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 4)
      - Visitors to Latin American Project, 1989-1991; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 5)
      - Working Papers: "The Case of the Missing Letter in Foreign Affairs: Kissinger, Pinochet and Operation Condor", 2004; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 6)
  - Keller, Kenneth H., 1990-1993; 10 folders
    - Asia, 1990; 1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 7)
    - Committees on Foreign Relations Program, 1992; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1993; 2 folders
      - President's Office, 1990-1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 9)
      - Vice President's Office, 1991-1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 10)
    - References for Technology Transfer, 1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 11)
    - Salinization Notes by Dunham, Sarah, circa 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 12)
    - Science in the Former Soviet Union, Planning and Background Research for Study Group, 1991-1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 13)
    - Senior Staff Retreat, 1993 March 12-13; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 14)
    - Sexual Harassment Policies, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 15)
    - Telecommunications, 1993; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 16)
  - Siegman, Henry, 1994; 4 boxes (1 partial)
    - Correspondence Files, Alphabetical, 1994; portions of 2 boxes
      - A, 1994; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 17)
      - B, 1994; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 18)
      - C, 1994; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 19)
      - D, 1994; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 20)
      - E, 1994; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 21)
      - F, 1994; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 22)
      - G, 1994; 1 folder (Box 421, Folder 23)
      - H, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 1)
      - I, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 2)
      - K, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 3)
      - L, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 4)
      - M, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 5)
      - N, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 6)
      - O, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 7)
      - P-Q, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 8)
      - R, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 9)
      - S, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 10)
      - T, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 11)
      - V, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 12)
      - W, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 13)
      - Z, 1994; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 14)
    - Meeting Files, Chronological, 1994 May 23-December 12; portions of 2 boxes
      - Shimon, Peres, 1994 May 23; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 15)
      - Arafat, Yasser, 1994 June 6; 1 folder (Box 422, Folder 16)
      - Roundtable Meeting, Crown Prince Hassan, 1994 October 2; 1 folder (Box 423, Folder 1)
      - Arafat, Yasser, 1994 November 17; 1 folder (Box 423, Folder 2)
      - Rubinstein, Eli, 1994 December 12; 1 folder (Box 423, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Files, 1994; 2 boxes (1 partial)
      - Committee on Studies, 1994 October 18; 1 folder (Box 423, Folder 4)
      - Mission to the Middle East, 1994 August; 2 folders (Box 423, Folder 5 to 6)
      - North African Economic Summit (Meeting Date, 1994 October 30 – November 1), 1994, 1 folder (Box 423, Folder 7)
      - North African Economic Summit (Meeting Date, 1994 October 30 – November 1), 1994, 3 folders (Box 424, Folder 1 to 3)
      - United States/Middle East Project, 1994; 1 folder (Box 424, Folder 4)